{
    "id": "55e212a8b3d04323ac89df51050c1d02",
    "title": "During, While And In",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met them ............................. I was holidaying in Canada.",
            "description": "While is a conjunction. We use it before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "142e5d1c28074aa9860d623ade4362b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met them .............................. my last holiday in Canada.",
            "description": "During is a preposition. We use it before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "38fd3d213a8849e38c9111da0255b874"
        },
        {
            "question": "Janet called .................................. you were out.",
            "description": "We use while before a clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "60ff142940924b768d8f514a3e465f1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she is not responsible for anything that happened .................................. her absence.",
            "description": "We use during before a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3183265990014cba8307518527227d1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I fell asleep ................................ I was reading the book.",
            "description": "We use a clause after while. ",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bd68101fa09e4f01a8414c5264eb1a8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had a lot of strange experiences ............................. our vacation in America.",
            "description": "We use a preposition after during.",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "in",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4c50b8ea4de743f78cf8b8f46feabeb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. holidaying in Melbourne, Jerry acquired a strong Australian accent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "While",
                "During",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9731240925d14d5daf0434e5898da93e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was in Mumbai .......................... the winter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8d31d2c6a3134cf39bd1c8378aae6d49"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will try to meet you ............................. my trip to California.",
            "description": "Use during before a noun/noun phrase.",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9c65a6f54cfb4793a50295c32aae2cd0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can I see you for a few minutes .............................. the afternoon?",
            "description": "Either during or in can be used to talk about the whole of the period.",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "in",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1f75de03dcb64eaca4e5ef9aa25a860d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't like to answer calls ................................. I am driving.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "52f38df3425446fd871b5455b3ecd361"
        },
        {
            "question": "The school was closed ............................. the whole of April.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b62175f7ae57474e90de92627d888384"
        }
    ]
}